

#### **PERSONAL**

Birthday : 25 June 1996
Nationality : Slovakian
Languages : English (C1)

German (B2) Slovak (Native) Hungarian (Native)

#### **LANGUAGES & SKILLS**

HTML MOTION ANIMATION

CSS / SCSS WEB & APP DESIGN

JS / JQUERY UX / UI DESIGN

PHP LOGO DESIGN

C# (C-SHARP) BRANDING

## **SOFTWARE & FRAMEWORKS**

PHOTOSHOP BOOTSTRAP
ILLUSTRATOR VUE.JS
AFTER EFFECTS WORDPRESS

ADOBE XD TYPO3

LOTTIE GIT / GITHUB & NPM
VS CODE HAPPY TO LEARN MORE!

### CONTACT

+45 25 13 27 87

pospi.sk

Hamburgerstraße 31, Heide, Germany

• Gravene 2C, 2, 4, Odense, Denmark

# KRISTIÁN POSPIŠ

web developer & designer

## **PROFILE**

I am a 24 year old web developer and multimedia designer. I have a passion for designing logos and creating web designs. Web development allows me to create something new that could potentionally help others meanwhile designing fulfils my creative thrist. The past year I have been gaining experience within front-end development at Boyens Medien in Heide, Germany. My main tasks were to create web and app designs for clients and in-house, afterwards code the design and finally integrate them into a CMS. I have spent 4 years studying web design and development in Odense, Denmark. The courses are structured around group projects where students have to solve tasks while new teams are formed every month. The group projects have made me a better team player but I can handle a project on my own as well. I am a perfectionist when it comes to design and a pragmatic thinker when it comes to programming. I like to double check my work and make sure that everything I create is up to modern standards.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **WEB DEVELOPMENT (B.SC.)**

UCL ODENSE 2017 - 2019

After receiving my AP degree I wanted to combine my design knowledge with web development so that I could create intuitive UI/UX designs, frontend tools/plugins and interactive content. I also gained experience in cross-platform app development using Xamarin Forms.

## **MULTIMEDIA DESIGN (AP)**

EAL ODENSE 2015 - 2017

Since I was 10 years old I have played around with Photoshop and after finishing highschool I wanted to study what I enjoyed doing in my freetime. When I have found a good school in Denmark I decided to move and learn more.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Jun 2019 - Sep 2020

Boyens-Medien GmbH & Co. KG | www.boyens-medien.de

At Boyens-Medien I was designing websites, UI, Apps and Logos. Most customer projects were TYPO3 based and I've worked on them individually. Occasionally we've worked in teams for larger projects.

# FULL-STACK DEVELOPER (INTERNSHIP) LISA.SK | www.lisa.sk

Aug 2018 - Nov 2018

During my web development studies at UCL I have interned at lisa.sk which is a slovakian web development company which provides the region and it's cities with government websites. I have learned more about web development best practices and found myself as a front-end developer.

## WEB DESIGNER (INTERNSHIP)

Feb 2017 - Jun 2017

Witt-Gruppe | www.witt-gruppe.eu

During my studies at MMD EAL I have interned at the Witt-Gruppe in Weiden, Germany as a web designer for four months. I was working 37 hours per week and gaining knowledge from my experienced co-workers.